<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on GREEN MACHINE</title>
    <link>https://buddhamagnet.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on GREEN MACHINE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>buddhamagnet</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 09:23:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://buddhamagnet.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the woods</title>
      <link>https://buddhamagnet.github.io/blog/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 09:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://buddhamagnet.github.io/blog/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;
So I start a two year journey in the woods near Appleton, Oxfordshire this weekend with Woodland Ways. Friday to Sunday in February. Needed a large pack so I could take everything I needed, and settled on the Atmos 65 from Osprey. Amazing piece of kit. Right now it&#39;s holding my tent, four season sleeping bag, cooking kit, axe and knife, clothes and
food and the only item outside is the self-inflating mat. The guy who reviews it below doesn&#39;t mention the built-in rain cover, but I&#39;m more
likely to need it than him.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;videoWrapper&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/66j34Z7vKRY&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
As for blades, haven&#39;t decided on a new knife as yet, but I&#39;ve packed a wildlife hatchet from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gransforsbruk.com/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gransfors Bruk&lt;/a&gt;. I&#39;ve had it for a few years and it&#39;s never let me down. Also the perfect size to take into the woods for a weekend.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;videoWrapper&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tH6SDh8pD2s&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
I tend to sleep on the ground in the colder months, and go up into a hammock as it gets warmer, so for this trip I&#39;ll be bedding down in the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.snugpak.com/outdoor/ionosphere-2577&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Snugpak Ionosphere&lt;/a&gt;. Goes up in a few minutes and surprisingly weather-proof.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div&gt;I try and pack everthing I need and no more, but it&#39;s February in the UK so my clothes comprise a Merino base layer and long johns, some trousers by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fjallraven.co.uk/vidda-pro-trousers-regular&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Fjallraven&lt;/a&gt;, and some waterpoof trousers and fleece, both by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.keela.co.uk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Keela&lt;/a&gt;. So I should be warm and dry. Now, to coat all this with the sweet smell of woodsmoke!
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>